full of brownie in backpack or nothing in packaging
all smooth
and today I will teach you
1 new crazy sales strategy
learn this
а ран
who is responsible
here today
I didn't come here to sell you
I came to give you 1 real gift
I created 1 brand
named Charlie Brown Junior
edible skate wheel
and Brown is the time you open it will notice he's Round
it is not square
and we are in packaging development
we put this prototype
here for you to meet leave
how did you get to know my brand first
I can leave you a little product there
you liked my product then we exchange
idea at the other time
I will write down your number
oh you don't even ask me to put it for sale
that one knows
ah Caião but it didn't sell
have to talk about sales at this time
let the guy
know my product
and then we exchange an idea brother
in two days i will be back
I have a cup of coffee
with you and we talk business bro
this is growth brother
Oh,
there's also the time here,
there are several poor things empty
brother so Charlie's homies
Brown and Junior invade the city
the idea is to create
belonging in the city of Santos and then opening
we create a relationship
then we see if it makes sense to close
beauty i can pick up here
what is this here the 3 thanks bro
wanted to leave 1 girl for you to meet
closed
bye bye
that's it my brother
1st test
brother gratitude we are together bro it's us bye
bye beauty
no beauty but this one is for you who will meet me
save this package that you will see in the scene
like Apple after
then the business got
when it comes to talking gosh this was the first one I will sell on the market
book
and so I will arrange demand
hand working 1 relationship
with people in 1 way
put in the faith that will flow
brother strategy strategy